One hour ago, OpenAI released GPT images
2.0 and it's great. It's fantastic.
>> You already tried it?
>> Yes. To make the thumbnail of this live
stream.
>> Cool.
>> So, but we are going to try it even more
together because Yeah. I want you to
like help me prompt some crazy stuff. a
state-of-the-art image model that can
take on complex visual task and produce
precise immediately usable visual with
sharper editing rich layout and syncing
level intelligence there is syncing into
this image model so it's interesting
because instead of like a loading open
AI logo into your image output you can
reference open AAI logo as and then it
will go as web search image is a step
change in details instruction following
Placing and yeah aka all of you print
are [__] You need to change
everything. Change your harness. Change
everything
>> again.
>> Detail instruction following placing and
object accurately and rendering dense
dense text with the ability to generate
across aspect ratio. They have way more
ratio than nano pro. Okay. A great
precision and control. Yeah. Okay.
That's cool.
>> That's hard.
>> Yeah. Damn. Like if if we're able to
generate that that's
>> Can you zoom in? Oh, see that's that's
really good.
>> Okay,
>> that would be cool if you eventually
found out they use the real image.
>> I mean, what do Yeah. What's What do you
mean like the real image?
>> Yeah, like a real photograph as an
example because it looks so good.
>> I mean, yeah. Like you can see like the
there is no like wrong artifact, right?
Like it looks like a real rice grain.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No longer persons with six
or seven fingers
>> at least. Not yet.
>> Yeah. But in this example, it generated
like after 20 hours of rendering.
>> But the same is here. At first, you had
the issue if you just want to print your
company name inside the image on a logo,
it would always make a typo. And now it
now it shows you a full letter.
>> That's not even like look like there is
like some different gray that
>> Yeah. Like the pen.
>> Yeah. And it Yeah. It looks like
different pressure of the world like of
the world. And there's even like a
coffee coffee mark on the top corner.
That's crazy. Let's play a little bit.
>> Yes. See what we can do.
>> Imagine Ellen Musk playing Diablo 3
buff. Elon Musk TV. Okay. What if Oh,
holy [__]
>> It put everything it it wrote down
around it.
>> So yeah, that's a character [__] So
yeah,
>> Ellen Musk technos sorcerer level 52.
Bro, that's sick. And that's the
interface from Diablo Diablo II. Boom.
Okay. So ratio. Okay. Okay. Nice. Okay.
Cool. And now, okay, put in the Diablo 3
game image is is a frame of three. Holy
[__]
>> Oh, that's cool. And he even put a Tesla
logo on his back.
>> Holy [__]
>> Wow.
>> You should DM it to Elon to see if you
can get a response.
>> Let's see how it goes. A manga page with
those with those two men. They are
meeting in the street. It's raining.
Midnight. Yeah, midnight dark time.
Okay, let's see.
>> Yeah. Now we can also see how fast it
is.
>> Not that fast.
>> Okay.
>> So, yeah, if you want to talk about
something else,
>> what did you do today? No.
>> Okay. Interesting. And about that. Okay.
We lost the faces, but
>> yeah, that doesn't matter.
>> Yeah, mine is more like Yeah, they got
we lost your reference, but okay, bro.
That's cool. You You made it. Yeah,
let's do this. Some conversation don't
just happen. They change everything to
night. What the make it not landscape
portrait. Okay. put these boxes with one
big central that going to and keep the
same face.
>> Yeah, you can make a full comic
>> 100%. Boom. Boom. Okay. So, okay. Which
sense do you read it? Because if if it's
a manga is going right to life, right?
You made it. Yeah. Let's do this. Boom.
Tonight we build the future. Some
conversation don't just happen. Okay.
The Okay, we need to we need to write to
think to work on the story. But
>> yeah, you also need to make a proper
prompt. Now it just copies the image.
>> I took a prompt from CL cuz I have a
conversation there. That's the that's
the first one it generated and I have
three different variation. It's cool. I
like I like this one.
>> Yeah. And it it only had one reference
image.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And I didn't upload the the
OpenAI logo.
>> No, no, it just found it. Well, at least
I know it has what the Open AI logo is.
>> Yeah. I asked it like to different
variation of the same prompt because I
edited inside the conversation and like
yeah it's not this one but okay so yeah
because I asked to show the different
capability of the model so different
type of illustration but then it had
like the GPT image and I didn't like
that yeah and that this one was another
variation but
>> to do it in Nana Banana 2 we had to put
in multiple images of the person right
>> no no just one like one output and stuff
so
>> okay there That was pretty similar.
Yeah. But even see between the face like
it's the same. Our face doesn't move. It
just like move it. But keep the
consistency between.
>> It's like it copy pasted the image.
>> Even here, same position, same
everything. Okay. The hand moved a bit.
But like my face doesn't change. Yours
neither. Yeah, it's it's crazy. Last
page of one is in live action from
Netflix video path. Okay. Did you watch
the TV show?
>> Just a few few a few one. Not the full
show.
>> That's all, bro. That's the [__]
actors.
>> And this is not a real scene, right?
This is creat. That's one of like all of
the some characters don't exist. Okay.
So, yeah, Brook is is only on his human
form like this here. This characters.
Okay. You don't see the mouse, but like
the this big guy on the right, it
doesn't is not happy yet. It's not
exactly that, but we are like 90% here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, it actually did a Google
search.
>> Yeah.
>> And it looked up all the characters and
put them in here.
>> What? So, you have What? Okay. And then
the pyro king disappear and then Okay.
>> The end.
>> It's weird.
Oh, that's good. It could have never
ruled, but it was never it was never the
point, bro. That's That's you can you
can Yeah, you can make a story board on
that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And if you play with it and
just keep improving your prompt, you can
make some really cool stuff.
>> Okay. something that you have been
struggling to generate with an image
model.
>> For example, if you have an office and
you want to write a company name on the
door, it's always giving issues.
>> Imagine
print with focus on the door with logo
>> ship [__] Ship [__] on the on it style.
>> Yes.
>> Window tinting auto residential.
>> It doesn't understand what ship [__] is.
>> Software development. Unix is user
friendly. That's good.
>> I mean I mean we have we have the we
have the name correct.
>> Pretty curious to see what other people
can do.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Like and it's full like it's copy
paste. Like the characters are copy
pasted. Nice. Nice. Nice. Okay. Cool.
That's it.
>> Well, it's time to make some images.
>> I was going to make some thumbnails in
the next few weeks for sure. We're going
to have some fun.
>> Yes. Well, looking forward to it.
>> Yes. Let's go. Let's go. Thank you,
Mitch, for your time. Thank you HGRA for
your participation and yeah if you are
here subscribe like the video too
please. Thank you because we need views
>> and follow us
>> and follow us everywhere and maybe Elon
Musk will do that soon. So yeah you
could say you will you you were there.
Let's go. Let's see.